chuckpalahniuk.net 2008-05-09

# Privacy Policy | The Cult

We at The Cult website ("Site") have created this policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within the Site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site located at the URL [www.ChuckPalahniuk.net](http://www.chuckpalahniuk.net/ "www.ChuckPalahniuk.net") or any successor site (the "Site"). We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy at this location.

**What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information:**

**Contact Information:** Some areas of our Site request or require contact and other information. During the registration process, we collect information such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address. Your contact information may be used to get in touch with you when necessary with respect to transactions conducted through the Site or for other internal purposes. We do not share your contact information with any third party without your consent, except to a court or governmental agency if permitted by law, as authorized by a court or to the limited extent described below under "Certain Third Party Transactions".

**Financial Information:** To conduct transactions through the Site, we may collect certain billing and financial information. Such information may include credit card numbers. We do not share your financial information with any third party without your consent, except to a court or governmental agency if permitted by law, as authorized by a court or to the limited extent described below under "Certain Third Party Transactions".

**Demographic Information:** Demographic and profile data (e.g., age and gender information) may also be collected at our Site. This data may be shared with advertisers or other third parties on an aggregated basis. We may also maintain a database of transactions on the Site and use this information in aggregate form to track the success of our Site.

**Internet Protocol Address:** We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site.

**Use of cookies:**

Our Site may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our Site. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.

**Public Forums:**

This Site may make chat rooms, message boards, and other postings on the Site available to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed by you becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security:**

This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, it is not possible to guaranty the security or integrity of information you disclose online since a sufficiently powerful attack from an unauthorized third party could compromise your data.

**Choice/Opt-Out:**

We may send communications regarding services, the Site or otherwise. You can opt-out of receiving such communications by indicating your desire to opt-out in an email sent to [webmaster@chuckpalahniuk.net](mailto:webmaster@chuckpalahniuk.net).

**Correct/Update:**

If any of your registration information changes or is incorrect, especially your email, please email us at [webmaster@chuckpalahniuk.net](mailto:webmaster@chuckpalahniuk.net) with your correct information.

**Certain Third Party Transactions:**

We may disclose personal information to third parties we engage to provide services that involve data processing on our behalf. Also, if some or all of the assets of our business are sold to a third party, that third party will be entitled to use the personal information disclosed by users of this Site, but only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Contacting the Web Site:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact our Web Site Administrator at [webmaster@chuckpalahniuk.net](mailto:webmaster@chuckpalahniuk.net) or A Writer's Cult, LLC, 3657 Mentone Avenue, #4, Los Angeles, CA 90034, USA.
